YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 8. Community Associations
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. SERVICES TO COMMUNITY ASSOCIATIONS
  - Subseries A. 1907-spring 1932
    - Reports
      - Town
        - Secretary annual, biennial, and periodic
          - Janet M. Smith, 1922 (Box 824, Folder 8)
          - Marie Lutters [Stanton], 1920 (Box 824, Folder 9)
          - Mary Stuart, 1918-19 (Box 824, Folder 10)
          - Edith Baldwin Terry, 1910-12 (Box 824, Folder 11)
          - Helen L. Thomas, 1911-14 (Box 824, Folder 12)
          - Sue Ann Wilson, 1920 (Box 824, Folder 13)
      - Rural Work
        - Department biennial reports, 1918-20, 1920-22, 1922-24, 1926-27, 1928-29 (Box 824, Folder 14-18)
        - Analysis of the Condition and Plans of the Rural Associations in the Eastern Region, n.d. (Box 824, Folder 19)
        - Report of the Discussion of Women's Programs, Aug 1930, Fletcher Farm (Box 824, Folder 20)
        - Statement regarding work of the Rural Communities Department, 23 Apr 1925 (Box 824, Folder 21)
        - Secretary annual, biennial, and periodic
          - Miscellaneous, 1920-31, n.d. (Box 824, Folder 22-23)
          - Mrs. R.H. Benham, 1921 (Box 824, Folder 24)
          - Eleanor Blackburn, 1928 (Box 824, Folder 25)
          - Elizabeth E. Blick, 1925-28 (Box 824, Folder 26)
          - Frances Bothwell, 1924 (Box 824, Folder 27)
          - Elsie I. Burnham, 1925-26 (Box 824, Folder 28)
          - Emma F. Byers, 1924 (Box 824, Folder 29)
          - Anna M. Clark
            - 1920-27 (Box 824, Folder 30-31)
            - 1928-31 (Box 825, Folder 1-2)
          - Gertrude Coon, 1922 (Box 825, Folder 3)
          - Eleanor Copenhaver, 1922-26 (Box 825, Folder 4)
          - Jane Dickey, 1926-31 (Box 825, Folder 5)
          - Lois Diehl, 1931 (Box 825, Folder 6)
          - Inez Ensign, 1927-31 (Box 825, Folder 7)
          - Helen N. Flack, 1924-31 (Box 825, Folder 8)
          - Margaret Forsyth, 1925 (Box 825, Folder 9)
          - Rhoda Foster, 1919-31 (Box 825, Folder 10-14)
          - M. Maud Fowler [Bristol], 1919-28 (Box 825, Folder 15-17)
          - Isora Sprague Gibson (Mrs. W. H.), 1924-29 (Box 825, Folder 18)
          - Mrs. John M. Hanna, 1925-27 (Box 825, Folder 19)
          - Marion W. Harmer, 1924-27 (Box 825, Folder 20)
          - Elizabeth B. Herring, 1922-31 (Box 825, Folder 21-24)
          - Elsie M. Hogsett (Mrs. L.M.), 1924-29 (Box 825, Folder 25)
          - M. Esther Huckins, 1926, 1931 (Box 825, Folder 26)
          - Helen Hutchinson, 1922-24 (Box 825, Folder 27)
          - Imogene B. Ireland, 1924-25 (Box 826, Folder 1)
          - Julia Lee, 1924 (Box 826, Folder 2)
          - Grace Nutting Miller, 1923-25 (Box 826, Folder 3)
          - Ethel Niermeyer, 1925-27 (Box 826, Folder 4)
          - Marjorie Patten, 1927-28 (Box 826, Folder 5)
          - Margaret Powell, 1924-26 (Box 826, Folder 6)
          - Irene Riley, 1925-31 (Box 826, Folder 7)
          - Henrietta Roelofs, 1924-30 (Box 826, Folder 8)
          - Elisabeth Rogers, 1925-31 (Box 826, Folder 9-10)
          - Emma Jewell Ross, 1922-29 (Box 826, Folder 11)
          - Helen B. Schuyler, 1926-28 (Box 826, Folder 12)
          - Lucy Sommerville, 1925-28 (Box 826, Folder 13)
          - Florence Stone, 1927 (Box 826, Folder 14)
          - Francelia Stuenkel, 1921-25 (Box 826, Folder 15-16)
          - Grace Stuff, 1926-27 (Box 826, Folder 17-18)
          - Adria Titterington, 1927-31 (Box 826, Folder 19)
          - Mildred D. Wilcox, 1929-31 (Box 826, Folder 20)
          - Hazel Bell Withrow, 1924-26 (Box 826, Folder 21)
    - Special Projects
      - Exposition Auxiliary Committee (Panama-Pacific Exposition, San Francisco 1915)
        - General and minutes, Apr-May 1915 (Box 826, Folder 22)
        - Reports
          - Exposition Extension Secretary (Alice Hoyt), Jul-Oct 1915 (Box 826, Folder 23)
          - Field Work Department Special Worker (Ella Schooley), Dec 1914-Dec 1915 (Box 826, Folder 24)
          - Cafeteria (Frances Holroyd), Mar-Oct 1915 (Box 826, Folder 25)
          - Club House on the Zone (Elizabeth Boies), Jun-Nov 1915 (Box 827, Folder 1)
          - Department Dealing with Women Employees of the Exposition (Thirmuthis Brookman), Apr-Dec 1915 (Box 827, Folder 2)
          - Emergency, Employment, Information, and Room and Board Departments (Alice Brookman and Grace Southwick), Mar-Dec 1915 (Box 827, Folder 3)
          - Office Work (E.W. Ristine), Jun-Oct 1915 (Box 827, Folder 4)
          - Religious Work (Julia Lee), Apr-Oct 1915 (Box 827, Folder 5)
      - Rural Communities Politics program, 1924, n.d. (Box 827, Folder 6)
    - Studies
      - General, 1924-31 (Box 827, Folder 7)
      - California
        - Orange County, California, by Clara S. Roe and Rhoda Foster, Nov-Dec 1925 (Box 827, Folder 8)
        - Pomona Valley, California, by Julia Tolman Lee and Rhoda Foster, Sep-Oct 1926 (Box 827, Folder 9)
        - Town-Rural Study of Riverside, Redlands, and San Bernardino Area of Southern California by Rhoda Foster and Clara S. Roe, Nov-Dec 1925 (Box 827, Folder 10)
        - Tulare County, California by Julia Tolman Lee and Rhoda Foster, 1925 (Box 827, Folder 11-13)
      - Idaho: Southern Idaho Project by Rhoda Foster, Helen N. Flack, and Isora Sprague Gibson, 1924-25 (to discover methods of organizing an Assn in a large area with scattered population and small financial resources) (Box 827, Folder 14)
      - Indiana by Hazel B. Withrow, 1924-26 (Box 827, Folder 15)
      - Iowa Study by Lois Diehl: preliminary report, Aug 1931 (Box 827, Folder 16)
      - Michigan
        - Development of the Young Women's Christian Association in the First Southern Michigan District (Hillsdale County, and Western Lenawee County), Jan 1923-Jan 1927 (Box 827, Folder 17-18)
        - Lansing Area by Julia Toman Lee and M. Maud Fowler, ca. 1926 (Box 828, Folder 1-2)
        - Report of the Town-Rural Study in Southern Michigan, May 1925 (Box 828, Folder 3)
        - Work in Hillsdale County, Michigan, by Inez Ensign, 1926-27 (Box 828, Folder 4)
        - The YWCA in Michigan: Lapeer District Rural Work, 1925-27; Grand Rapids Area Rural Work, ca. 1926 and Wexford County Rural Work, ca. 1927 (Box 828, Folder 5)
      - Oklahoma: The Northeast Oklahoma District YWCA by D. Katharine Rogers, Nov 1926 (Box 828, Folder 6)
      - Ohio: The Tecumseh District YWCA by D. Katharine Rogers, Jul 1926 (Box 828, Folder 7-9)
      - Texas
        - Dallas and Galveston-Houston Districts, Texas, by Margaret Williamson and Emma Jewell Ross, May 1927 (Box 828, Folder 10)
        - Urban-Rural Economic Study of the Dallas and Houston-Galveston Districts of the YWCA by R. Clyde White, 15 Sep 1926 (Box 828, Folder 11)
      - Wisconsin
        - Study of the YWCA of Wausau, Wisconsin by Clara Strong Roe, May 1928 (Box 828, Folder 12)
        - Report of the Town-Rural Study in Southern Wisconsin, Oct 1924 (Box 828, Folder 13)
      - Rural-Industrial Study by Eleanor Copenhaver, Jul 1924 (Box 828, Folder 14)
      - Rural-Industrial Section (Soft Coal Communities, Steel and Lead Communities, Southern Textile Communities) by Eleanor Copenhaver, Margaret Forsyth, Donald McConnell, Dorothy P. Gary, and Lois MacDonald, [1926] (Box 828, Folder 15-18)
      - Student-Rural Community Study by Gladys Taylor, [1925] (Box 828, Folder 19)
      - Town-Rural Relationships by Francelia Stuenkel and Clara S. Roe: general, Jul 1924 (Box 828)
    - OVERSIZE (Box 829)
      - "Town Book, Tenth Anniversary," scrapbook given to Town Department Executive, Anna Seaburg, 1926, [photographs and text re associations organized under the "Town Plan," 1916-26] (Box 829)
  - Subseries B. Fall 1932-2001
    - Department/Division
      - National Services Division (fall 1932-spring 1940)
        - General and History, 1935-38 (Box 830, Folder 1)
        - "Brief History," Report of National Services Division, 1931-37 by Lucy P. Carner (Box 830, Folder 2)
        - Minutes
          - National Services Division/National Services Division Committee
            - Oct 1931-Jul 1940 (Box 830, Folder 3-10)
          - National Services Division Staff
            - Jan 1932-Aug 1936 (Box 830, Folder 11-19)
            - Aug 1936-Jul 40 (Box 831, Folder 1-8)
      - Community Division (fall 1940-71)
        - General and History, 1941-71 (Box 831, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence re YWCA Constitution revision and interpretation, 1955-71 (Box 831, Folder 10-15)
        - Minutes
          - Community Division Committee
            - Charter, 1958; and index to minutes, 1940-46 (Box 832, Folder 1)
            - Minutes
              - 1940-54 (Box 832, Folder 2-11)
              - 1955-70 (Box 833, Folder 1-7)
          - Community Division Core Group, 1970-71 (Box 833, Folder 8)
      - Organization Development Unit (1972-84)
        - General, 1972-83 (Box 833, Folder 9)
        - Buildings Consultant
          - General, 1970-81 (Box 833, Folder 10-11)
          - Ohio
            - Cleveland, 1970-80 (Box 833, Folder 12)
            - Columbus, 1975-80 (Box 833, Folder 13)
            - Dayton, 1970-81 (Box 833, Folder 14)
            - Lancaster, 1971-75 (Box 833, Folder 15)
            - Licking County, 1970-78 (Box 833, Folder 16)
            - Mansfield, 1973-76 (Box 833, Folder 17)
            - Medina, 1970-78 (Box 833, Folder 18)
            - Springfield, 1974-75 (Box 833, Folder 19)
            - Toledo, 1971-81 (Box 833, Folder 20)
            - Youngstown, 1975-80 (Box 833, Folder 21)
          - Oklahoma, 1970-74 (Box 834, Folder 1)
          - Pennsylvania, 1974-75 (Box 834, Folder 2)
      - Services to Urban Associations
        - General, 1971-83 (Box 834, Folder 3-4)
        - Urban Services Committee/Urban Affairs Committee: minutes, 1974-79 (Box 834, Folder 5)
      - Field Services Division: general, 1978-91, n.d. (Box 834, Folder 6-7)
      - Member Association Services (1992-2001)
        - General, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 834, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 834, Folder 9-12)
        - Financial and budget, 1992-95 (Box 834, Folder 13)
        - Job descriptions, 1994, 1999, n.d. (Box 835, Folder 1)
        - Office forms and record keeping procedures, 1992-2000, n.d. (Box 835, Folder 2-3)
        - Unemployment insurance program for Member Associations, 1996 (Box 835, Folder 4)
    - Committees and Task Forces
      - Community Division Subcommittees
        - Miscellaneous, 1942-48 (Box 835, Folder 5)
        - Accredited YWCA, 1966 (Box 835, Folder 6)
        - Administration, 1946, 1969 (Box 835, Folder 7)
        - Association Review, 1968 (Box 835, Folder 8)
        - Camping, 1966 (Box 835, Folder 9)
        - Membership Study Group, 1959-60 (Box 835, Folder 10)
        - Membership, 1964-65 (Box 835, Folder 11)
        - New Organization, 1968 (Box 835, Folder 12)
        - Personal and Family Relations, 1941-42 (Box 835, Folder 13)
        - Racial Integration, 1966 (Box 835, Folder 14)
        - Residence Study, 1968 (Box 835, Folder 15)
        - Teenage Program, 1964-66 (Box 835, Folder 16)
        - Young Adult, 1964-66 (Box 835, Folder 17)
      - Organization Development Task Forces, 1983-84 (Box 835, Folder 18)
      - Member Association Services
        - Consistent Messages Work Group, 1995 (Box 835, Folder 19)
        - National/Local Relations Task Force, 1990-93 (Box 835, Folder 20)
        - Racial Justice Committee, 1993-94, n.d. (Box 835, Folder 21)
        - Task Groups, 1995 (Box 835, Folder 22)
    - Community Associations
      - Accreditation and Affiliation
        - General, 1991-96 (Box 835, Folder 23)
        - Audit Accreditation Reports, 1990-92 (Box 835, Folder 24)
        - Status reports, 1993-2001, n.d. (Box 835, Folder 25-26)
        - Disaffiliation, general, 1997-98 (Box 836, Folder 1)
        - Mid-cycle Affiliation Requirements contact all sheets, 2001? (Box 836, Folder 2)
        - Probationary status
          - General, 1995-98 (Box 836, Folder 3)
          - Associations on probation, Oct 1996 (Box 836, Folder 4)
        - YWCA Retirement Fund participation, 2000-2001 (Box 836, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 836, Folder 6-7)
        - Legal issues and agreements
          - General, 1992-96, n.d. (Box 836, Folder 8)
          - Mailing re EEOC v. YWCA of Tucson, 1992 (Box 836, Folder 9)
          - Nine West Group, Inc., settlement funding, 2000 (Box 836, Folder 10)
      - Financial
        - Finance data from Member Associations, 1991-94 (Box 836, Folder 11-14)
        - National Support/National Affiliation Dues
          - General, 1991-2000 (Box 836, Folder 15)
          - Formula
            - Requests for proposals for developing a new formula, 1997 (Box 836, Folder 16)
            - A.T. Kearney, Inc.: report and presentations on dues formula, 1997-98 (Box 837, Folder 1)
          - Payment status reports, 1996-98 (Box 837, Folder 2)
          - Reports, 1991-99 (Box 837, Folder 3)
        - Revolving Loan Assistance Fund, 1997, n.d. (Box 837, Folder 4)
      - Guidelines, Forms, and Publications
        - Grace H. Dodge Merit Fellowship Award, ca. 2000 (Box 837, Folder 5)
        - Geographical Reviews: draft, 1996 (Box 837, Folder 6)
        - Membership Chairpersons and Membership Committees in Community YWCAs, Mar 2000 (Box 837, Folder 7)
      - Programs offered by Member Associations
        - General, 1996, 1998 (Box 837, Folder 8-9)
        - Aquatics, n.d. (Box 837, Folder 10)
        - Camps, 1990 (Box 837, Folder 11)
        - Child Abuse, 1995 (Box 837, Folder 12)
        - Domestic Violence, 1994, 1998 (Box 837, Folder 13)
        - Elderly Care, 1995 (Box 837, Folder 14)
        - Employment Assistance, 1994 (Box 837, Folder 15)
        - Employment Training, 1996 (Box 837, Folder 16)
        - Fitness, n.d. (Box 837, Folder 17)
        - HIV/AIDS, 1997 (Box 837, Folder 18)
        - Pools, 1998 (Box 837, Folder 19)
        - Prison/Ex-Prison, 1993 (Box 837, Folder 20)
        - Rape Crisis Hotline, 1991 (Box 837, Folder 21)
        - Residences, 1992-98 (Box 837, Folder 22)
        - Sexually Transmitted Diseases, 1999-2000 (Box 837, Folder 23)
        - Transitional Housing, 1993 (Box 837, Folder 24)
        - Tribute Ceremonies, 1994 (Box 838, Folder 1)
        - Wellness/Healthy Lifestyles, n.d. (Box 838, Folder 2)
        - Women Entrepreneurs, 1998 (Box 838, Folder 3)
        - Widow/Divorce Support Groups, 1994 (Box 838, Folder 4)
      - Questionnaires and surveys to Member Associations
        - Financial Development, 1998 (Box 838, Folder 5-7)
        - Software, 1992 (Box 838, Folder 8)
    - Conferences and Meetings
      - Big City Conference, 1948 (Box 838, Folder 9)
      - Consultation: Alternatives to Building, 1975 (Box 838, Folder 10)
      - Forums on National/Local Partnership, spring 1983 (Box 838, Folder 11)
      - Metropolitan Seminars, 1973-2001 (Box 838, Folder 12-15)
    - Programs and Projects
      - Action Plan [to accelerate racial integration in community YWCAs]
        - Subcommittee on the Action Plan: minutes, 1963-65 (Box 838, Folder 16)
        - Correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 838, Folder 17)
        - Leadership Kit for Community YWCA Action Program, 1964 (Box 838, Folder 18)
        - Mailings, 1963-64 (Box 839, Folder 1)
        - Reference materials, 1960-63, n.d. (Box 839, Folder 2)
        - Reports, 1963-65 (Box 839, Folder 3-5)
        - Work tools, 1963-64 (Box 839, Folder 6)
      - Agricultural Committee Projects: number 4 "Do Farm Prices Just Happen?" and number 5 "How Much Security Has the Farmer?," 1938 (Box 839, Folder 7)
      - Residence Survey, 1936-39 (Box 839, Folder 8)
      - Rural Work
        - General, 1937-53 (Box 839, Folder 9)
        - District YWCAs, 1936-39 (Box 839, Folder 10)
      - Study Project on Administration of Metropolitan and Selected One-Branch YWCAs, Harleigh B. Trecker, 1958 (Box 839, Folder 11)
      - Study Project on Administration of YWCAs in Changing Communities, 1959 (Box 839, Folder 12)
      - Special Project on New Organization, 1960-61 (Box 839, Folder 13)
    - Publications
      - Area Planning-Implications for the YWCA, 1965 (Box 839, Folder 14)
      - Before the YWCA Builds: A Building Manual, 1957, 1967 (Box 839, Folder 15)
      - Branch Relationships and Branch By-Laws (A Revision), 1946 (Box 840, Folder 1)
      - A Building Manual for the YWCA: Part 1, Guidelines for Implementing a Building Program, 1978 (Box 840, Folder 2)
      - A Building Manual for the YWCA: Part 2, Design Guidelines for New or Renovated Buildings, 1981 (Box 840, Folder 3)
      - The Community YWCA and its Community Chest Relations, a worktool prepared by Genevieve Lowry, 1952 (Box 840, Folder 4)
      - Decentralized Units of Program, 1953-58 (Box 840, Folder 5)
      - Form of Organization for the Small Association, 1950 (Box 840, Folder 6)
      - Getting Your Annual Meeting Squared Away, Feb 1984 (Box 840, Folder 7)
      - Guidelines for YWCAs Considering Consolidation, 1969 (Box 840, Folder 8)
      - How We Build: Visual Presentation of Function and Space, 1949 (Box 840, Folder 9)
      - Leader's Guide for Unstaffed YWCA Units, 1965 (Box 840, Folder 10)
      - Membership Pointers for Community YWCA's, 1949, 1951 (Box 840, Folder 11)
      - One YWCA: On the Campus-In the Community, 1958 (Box 840, Folder 12)
      - The Operation of Housing and Building Services (Including Rooms Registry and Referral Services) for Community Associations, circa 1950 (Box 840, Folder 13)
      - Organizing a New YWCA, n.d. [missing Part 1], Jun 1997, Dec 2001 (Box 840, Folder 14-16)
      - Organizing a New YWCA: Stage Two, The Provisional Stage, 1974 (Box 841, Folder 1)
      - Procedures and Forms for Use in Developments of Community YWCAs: Staff Work Tool, 1967, 1974, 1980 (Box 841, Folder 2-3)
      - Program and Structure in Community YWCAs, Staff Work Notes, 1947 (Box 841, Folder 4)
      - Record keeping, 1978, 1983 (Box 841, Folder 5)
      - Registered YWCA Groups, Kit of Organizing Material, 1975 (Box 841, Folder 6)
      - The Residence and the YWCA: typescript and published version, 1954 (Box 841, Folder 7-8)
      - "Search Committee Guidelines for Executive Director and Interim Executive Director of the YWCA of the USA," 2001 (Box 841, Folder 9)
      - "Study Guide for Determining the Need for a YWCA Residence," 1961 (Box 841, Folder 10)
      - What Can We Expect of Rural Schools, Mildred Cranston, 1948 (Box 841, Folder 11)
      - When We Build: Some hints and hunches collected from here and there, 1952 (Box 841, Folder 12)
      - YWCA Handbook: A Guide for Community Units of District YWCAs, 1940 (Box 841, Folder 13)
      - YMCA-YWCA Cooperation, 1956-69 (Box 841, Folder 14)
      - Serials
        - "Information Briefs" from Executive Bulletin, 1975-78 (Box 841, Folder 15)
        - Network News, 1993-98 (Box 841, Folder 16)
        - Council Gram, 1994-96 (Box 841, Folder 17)
    - Regional Staff and Councils
      - General, 1933-99, n.d. (Box 842, Folder 1-7)
      - Regional Field Managers
        - Correspondence, 1992-2001 (Box 842, Folder 8-9)
        - Meetings, 1999-2001 (Box 842, Folder 10)
      - Regions charts, 1940-89, n.d. (Box 842, Folder 11)
      - Regional staff assignments, 1964-65 (Box 842, Folder 12)
      - Northwest Conference, Menucha, Oregon, Nov 1980 (Box 842, Folder 13)
      - Multi-State Convocations re national-local relationship "Strengthening the Ties That Bind," Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1997-99 (Box 843, Folder 1)
      - Arkansas/Arkansas-Texarcana, 1989-94 (Box 843, Folder 2)
      - Carolina Cluster, 1974-98, n.d. (Box 843, Folder 3)
      - Central Region, 1949-57 (Box 843, Folder 4)
      - Connecticut, 1993-98 (Box 843, Folder 5)
      - Council of Illinois and St. Louis YWCAs (CISLY), 1992-2000 (Box 843, Folder 6)
      - Dakotas, 1994-2001 (Box 843, Folder 7)
      - Delta (Arkansas, Louisiana, Mississippi, and Mobile, Alabama), 1998 (Box 843, Folder 8)
      - Eastern Region, 1955-69 (Box 843, Folder 9)
      - Florida-Georgia (sometimes known as Georgia-Florida), 1996-98 (Box 843, Folder 10)
      - Great Lakes Alliance (Ohio, Michigan, Wisconsin, Indiana, Illinois, and St. Louis), 1999-2000 (Box 843, Folder 11)
      - Hawaii, 1993-98 (Box 843, Folder 12)
      - Heartland (Missouri, Nebraska, Kansas), 1989-2001 (Box 843, Folder 13)
      - Indiana, 1997-99 (Box 843, Folder 14)
      - Iowa, 1993-98 (Box 843, Folder 15)
      - Kentucky-Tennessee/Alabama-Kentucky-Tennessee, 1991-98 (Box 843, Folder 16)
      - Louisiana, 1995-98 (Box 843, Folder 17)
      - Michigan, 1992-2000 (Box 843, Folder 18)
      - Mid-Atlantic (Delaware, D.C., Maryland), 1998, n.d. (Box 843, Folder 19)
      - Minnesota, 1986-2000, n.d. (Box 844, Folder 1)
      - New England, 1993-99, n.d. (Box 844, Folder 2)
      - New Jersey, 1994-2001 (Box 844, Folder 3)
      - New York State, 1992-2000, n.d. (Box 844, Folder 4)
      - New York and New Jersey, 1907 (Box 844, Folder 5)
      - Northeast, 1996-97 (Box 844, Folder 6)
      - Northeast Alliance (Haverhill, Newburyport, and Malden, Mass.), 1997-98, n.d. (Box 844, Folder 7)
      - Northern California (NorCal), 1982-99, n.d. (Box 844, Folder 8)
      - Northwest YWCA Coalition/Pacific Northwest Coalition (Alaska, Washington, Idaho, Montana, Oregon), 1995-2001 (Box 844, Folder 9)
      - Ohio
        - 1983-96 (Box 844, Folder 10)
        - 1997-2001, n.d. (Box 845, Folder 1)
      - Oklahoma, 1993-96 (Box 845, Folder 2)
      - Pennsylvania, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 845, Folder 3-4)
      - Rocky Mountain, 1993-98 (Box 845, Folder 5)
      - Southern Region, 1956-69 (Box 845, Folder 6)
      - Southern California (SoCal)
        - 1983-98 (Box 845, Folder 7-10)
        - 1999-2000 (Box 846, Folder 1)
      - Southwest/Texas (Arizona, Texas, and Albuquerque, NM), 1988-2002, n.d. (Box 846, Folder 2)
      - Virginia, 1992-97 (Box 846, Folder 3)
      - West Virginia, 1996-99 (Box 846, Folder 4)
      - Western Region, 1957, 1965-69 (Box 846, Folder 5)
      - Wisconsin, 1989-98, n.d. (Box 846, Folder 6)
    - Reports
      - General
        - Report of special staff meetings considering adjustment of policies and practices for local associations, Jan 1933 (Box 846, Folder 7)
        - Progress of Rural Associations, 1938-40 (Box 846, Folder 8)
        - Report of Registered YWCAs, 1940 (Box 846, Folder 9)
        - Summary report of responses to questionnaire on residences included as a supplement in 1951 Annual Statistical Report forms, 1952 (Box 846, Folder 10)
        - "Greenleigh Report" by Arthur Greenleigh, Greenleigh Associates Management Consultants, re operations, structure, and service of the National Board Office, 1958 [copy also in Reorganizations] (Box 846, Folder 11)
        - Analysis and summaries by Lois Diehl of studies made by various groups between 1955 and 1961 of YWCA Community Associations, Feb-Mar 1962
          - Analysis and overall summary (Box 846, Folder 12)
          - Detailed summaries
            - Central Region (Box 846, Folder 13)
            - Eastern Region (Box 846, Folder 14)
            - Southern Region (Box 846, Folder 15)
            - Western Region (Box 846, Folder 16)
        - Membership Analysis, 1994, 2000 (Box 847, Folder 1)
        - Report of the Program-Planning Studies, 1931-33 by Mildred H. Esgar (Box 847, Folder 2)
        - Small Associations, 1967 (Box 847, Folder 3)
      - Staff
        - Buildings Consultant, Iris Alex, 1971-81 (Box 847, Folder 4-5)
        - Organization Development, Unit Executive, 1973-80 (Box 847, Folder 6-7)
        - Member Associations Services Office
          - General, 1992-98 (Box 847, Folder 8)
          - Staff monthly reports, 1996-2001, n.d. (Box 847, Folder 9-12)
    - Training
      - General, 1952, 1997-98 (Box 847, Folder 13)